https://moyerinstruments.com/privacy-policy-2/

Skip to content
Home Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
The Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you decide to share, and help you make informed decisions when using the moyerinstruments.com web site. By using or accessing moyerinstruments.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
To protect our members’ privacy, moyerinstruments.com cloaks the actual identity of our members. Members are identified on the site by username. If you have questions or concerns regarding this policy, you should contact our staff at
From time to time, we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post those changes on the Web Site so Members and other users of the moyerinstruments.com Web Site are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Non-material changes and clarifications will take effect immediately. Interwebshop Internet Services.com may modify this Privacy Policy Agreement from time to time and such modification shall be effective upon posting by moyerinstruments.com on the moyerinstruments.com Website. You agree to be bound to any changes to this Agreement when you use moyerinstruments.com after any such modification are posted. It is therefore important that you review this Agreement regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.
Privacy Policy
This site is owned and operated by moyerinstruments.com. Your privacy on the Internet is of the utmost importance to us. At moyerinstruments.com, we want to make your experience online satisfying and safe.
Because we gather certain types of information about our users, we feel you should fully understand our policy and the terms and conditions surrounding the capture and use of that information. This privacy statement discloses what information we gather and how we use it.
1. Collection of Data
We do not track, collect or distribute personal information about visitors of our website. We only tracks information about the visits to our web sites. For example, we compile statistics that show the daily number of visitors to our sites, the daily requests we receive for particular files on our web sites, and what countries those requests come from. These aggregated statistics are used to better provide services to the public and may also be provided to others, but again, the statistics contain no personal information and cannot be used to gather such information. However, if you decided to register on our website, forum and purchase any of our products your personal information required by register process will be added to our user database. If at any time you change your mind and would like to be removed from our user database we shall delete all your personal data.
2. Use of Data
We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.
3.No Release/Share/Sell of Information
Your personal information will not be released to third parties and shared among other users except to further the purpose for which you had provided the information, such as making specific requests for information, or if you request that your email be forwarded. There are no other circumstances under which we will provide or sell personal information to third parties.
4.No Sell of User List
We do not sell user list of our users to any third party company for any further purposes. All information about our users are stored in the password protected database installed in secure server hosting machine.
5. Cookies
Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site.
6. Children
We do not allow persons who are ages 17 or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact moyerinstruments.com at .
7. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information
We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration by using your personal page configuration area. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting our webmaster. Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.
8. Changes to this Privacy Policy
We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.
9. No Guarantees.
While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
10. Google Analytics.
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. Google. Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website including your IP address will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Googles behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser. However please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
YOUR CONSENT
By using this site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by moyerinstruments.com. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
Questions or comments
If you have questions or comments about this policy or if you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy please contact us at .
